Ramanjit Kaur Sandhu

96 wall park Avenue Blacktown

2148

Phone number 0469787139.

**Professional Summary** 

I am an experienced professional in the care industry seeking a role with your organisation because I believe you make an impact in the lives of people every day. I have over 5 years of experience in the industry. I'm certain my experience can help your organisation grow to support more people.

## **Qualifications**

Advanced diploma in hospitality Management.

Diploma in nursing.

Certificate in 3 age care.

Certificate 4 In disability.

Diploma in community service started this year in January.

First AID.

Epilepsy training.

Wound Care training.

## Work Experience

Disability support worker, January 2017 to 2019 as Homecare .

Help clients with household chores such as cleaning, cooking and pet care

Develop a working relationship with clients to determine their needs

Assist clients with personal hygiene

Write reports about services I provide

Create a schedule to help regulate client health and satisfaction.

Disability support worker with unisson disability from 2020 to till now

Flintwood disability from December 2021 to December 2022.

Support clients to participate in age appropriate

Activities and tasks including employment, in home

Support and community access.

Support clients to access activities and outings in The community.

Provide direct care assistance to each client in Accordance with their service plan and as directed By the Manager.

Work in accordance with the medication Administration policy.

Participate in the Lifestyle Service Planning Process for individual clients and monitor Outcomes.

Work with clients, family/ carers, relevant case
Managers and other professionals to support the

Client's individual goals.

In conjunction with other members of staff assist in Developing, implementing and evaluating training And behaviour programs to attain identified Individual goals.

Ensure that all programming undertaken is

Appropriately maintained, documented and
Reviewed.

Assume the role of key worker for designated Clients, including the preparation of a monthly Report on client progress.

Running my cafe business from 2017 till now Leadership.

Considering options.

Creating a business plan.

Ergonomics and aesthetics.

Managing finances.

Staff management.

Menu crafting.

Customer relations.

Referee will be provided on request.